That's really good insurance by the way.
Oh, thanks.
Oh, well mine.
Oh.
I don't know what yours is yet.
I don't know what yours is.
So you need a page like this.
Yes.
Because I'm going to see the coverages.
Okay.
So.
Let me see.
And also, because I wanted to get a checkup, but I was hoping like the other party could
pay for it.
But the issue is, I'm actually leaving on Tuesday.
Where are you going to?
To Utah.
Yeah.
What's for?
Like, it's like a program for active element, like, like, perhaps and stuff.
So that's wondering, like, is there a whole nother conversation?
Yeah.
Is there like enough time to?
So.
Let me think.
Like, I was hoping today, or is it possible?
What are you leaving Tuesday?
Tuesday morning.
Then just go to, um, quick care.
Do you have insurance?
Yeah, I do.
Okay.
Good.
Let me go and copy that too.
Is it okay to use my insurance?
That's okay.
Okay.
That's the best way.
Just go to, like, quick care.
Ish.
Um, it really depends.
Yeah.
Quick care is fine.
Yes.
Karen.
Emma.
Good.
Um, do you need, like, the, do you need a photo of it?
Like, just the information, or do you need, like, the copy?
Yeah.
You can just give me a photo.
Okay.
You can give me a photo of your insurance card that's fine too.
Don't you have my insurance card?
I don't think I do.
I don't think I got that one.
The health insurance one.
Oh, okay.
Have you ever had any prior accidents or no?
Um, a very minor one.
Like, it was just like a little bump in the back.
Like, it was at the red lights.
Nobody ever made a claim or anything or open a claim?
I think I made a claim.
Yeah.
Well, I had their insurance.
When was it?
Oh, this was like, probably going to go over here.
Yeah.
It was just like, we're out of stock.
Like, I see thought it was green in my, the back of my card.
So.
Okay.
Got it.
Do you have any other claims, slip and fall?
Work call for anything?
No.
Okay.
We need to get your car towed out.
But we won't be able to because your dad's right?
Is it your dad's car?
It's mine, yeah.
You own the car.
Yeah.
Oh.
Is it insurance in your dad's name?
So your dad needs to call down there and get it towed.
You can either get it towed to a body shop of your choice.
We have one that we can recommend too.
Or you can get towed to your house and then you have to get towed to the body shop.
Because the tow yard, they charge you like, craving amounts a day.
Like, they have $500 a day.
So you want to get it towed out.
Okay.
Yeah.
Because you have a duty to mitigate.
So you have to duty to like, kind of reduce your costs.
Like, you can't just run up the cost of the party's paying for it.
Yeah.
So you have to like, take that car out.
Okay.
So get your dad.
It should be a problem there.
Yeah.
Cause your dad will have to, cause we don't represent your dad.
So.
Okay.
I mean, just get that out as soon as possible.
How long are you going through this app course?
Like, three and a half months.
Yeah.
Cause your dad will have to, cause we don't represent your dad.
So.
Okay.
I mean, just get that out as soon as possible.
Like, three and a half months.
So.
Okay.
We'll catch you someone.
Where are you going to be?
Um.
Salt Lake City.
Yeah.
I know it just happened right before.
About the leaves that kind of sucks.
Okay.
That's cool though.
I should send my brother to that, but he is cool.
Yeah.
I've been thinking about for a long time.
Fine.
There's a red to coder or coder.com.
Have you heard of it?
I heard of those said websites.
Yeah.
I think I did like a few of those.
Cause yeah.
I would have to do like a.
Like a.
Program for like personal injury.
Oh, yeah.
It'd be cool.
Maybe I've done that and I could help you make one.
I don't know if it would be an app.
It'd be like a program.
I don't know if they do that.
Like a website.
Like upload.
Like it.
They should just have checklists.
Like I need the first.
I need the police report.
You know, I need the help.
Oh, yeah.
So you said it to your client.
Yeah.
I think I know everything.
Coving is like once you know one kind of like.
Know the other a little bit.
But.
Yeah.
It shouldn't be too long.
Okay.
So you will find you one.
Get in it.
That's probably the go on.
Okay.
So there's a few.
Um, sorry.
Act to my thing.
If you do get a repair estimate anywhere.
Is it a pretty bad accident?
Sounds like.
Yeah.
Okay.
So if you get a.
Do you think it'll be fixed?
Or.
The guy told me like.
80%.
You're going to probably not be able to fix it.
So just get it to your house then.
Okay.
Because you don't live in an age way community.
Yeah.
That's why I asked.
Never.
Try not to do it, actually.
Okay.
Um, so call my insurance.
If I do have a 20 servers until it's in my house, right?
Right.
Um, they were going to send someone to do like an estimate.
Try to actually let them know.
Yeah.
Okay.
You should.
Let them know that it's at your house.
Yeah.
Okay.
Because this is what happens.
Um, let's say they look at your Kelly's blue book of your car.
Let's say it's 10 grand.
Okay.
Let's say you left it at the tow yard for two weeks.
And they'll charge you two weeks time.
Whatever it is.
$300 a day.
You know, $14.
Yeah.
3600.
Then they'll take that off your 10 grand.
So you don't want that.
They won't tell you.
Yeah.
They'll tell you.
They'll send you a letter saying, dude.
You have a.
Yeah.
Reduce your cost.
Mitigate.
Yeah.
Okay.
But if you do get a repair estimate, let me know.
I think they did not.
So I'll play.
Hopefully nothing.
And give me the estimate.
Okay.
Next thing.
I gave you the text line.
You should save it under like attorney.
Are you coming back afterwards?
Yeah.
I'll be back for like a couple of months.
And then.
Do you know where you go?
Yeah.
I'll be back for like a couple of months.
And then.
Did you know where you go?
Yeah.
It's.
It's pretty.
Like big move.
Yeah.
So exciting.
Anyway.
So.
Yeah.
Save it as like a law officer.
Law officer.
Law firm.
I'm.
Just in case you need it.
Remember.
I'll save it.
Okay.
Yeah.
It's a text line.
So don't call it.
Because people will be answering.
Okay.
To remind people that.
I'm like.
Yeah.
Oh.
It's going to pick up.
Okay.
Yeah.
You can call the main line if you need to call.
And then.
Can you text me a picture of you?
So I can put it on the file too.
Okay.
And it's not like a real text.
Like it sends it.
This program is supposed to save us like.
Um.
Yeah.
And it's not like a real text.
Like it sends it.
This program is supposed to save us like.
Um.
From being distracted.
We easily get distracted.
So it sends us alerts like twice a day.
Like that people text it.
So like if you're like,
Hey, I need something.
I'm like standing outside.
Yeah.
I won't get it right away.
Okay.
It's not like I'm carrying around my phone.
Like we answer your text.
Okay.
So we want like lifetime clients who refer us.
Their friends and family.
So we want to teach you everything to do in an accident.
Because it ever happens again.
Yeah.
Sometimes this happens again.
Most of the time you don't want to talk to the insurance company.
They're not your friends.
So next time call us before you talk to them because we'll.
They're just not your friends.
Okay.
What else?
Um.
You can speak to the gesture about the property damage.
It's just not about the accident or the injuries.
And that's why we don't want people to do that.
The insurance company.
You can talk to them about your car.
Like, hey, I need my car fix.
I need a rental.
Nothing about injuries.
Okay.
Yeah.
Because then they try and like get you on it later.
They'll be like, you just told me about your back.
You just told me about your neck or your headache.
You didn't tell me about your back or your leg.
Okay.
Well, it started hurting two days later.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
So things happen though in two days or whatever.
You might start hurting some more.
Um.
And then they, like one of my clients yesterday, like I talked to them.
And then they told me it was my fault.
My own insurance company.
And I'm like, that's why you need us to talk to them.
Yeah.
Sometimes we get confused and they can't explain it.
Like when you tell me I like, like write it out.
Like sometimes people write it out.
And I'm like, I still understand what you just said.
I just rewrite it.
You know.
Um.
What else?
So property damage usually takes.
It may take two weeks to 30 days.
Okay.
Unless she really comes out and says that she did it.
Mm-hmm.
You know, maybe in this case, you will.
Because there's a lot of witness, too.
There's a lot of witnesses.
Right.
I think that a driver, like she knew it was her fault.
I've seen it crazy, though.
I've seen like two police reports where it's like totally their fault.
And they're like, no, it's not my fault.
Oh.
It's not my fault.
And they're like, my client's like, when do I get a car?
I'm like, do you have insurance on your, you know, on your insurance?
Because people like don't get rental insurance on their cars and all the other stuff.
And then they're like, how can I get my car fixed?
I'm like, just because someone hits you, doesn't mean they automatically fix your car or give you money for your car.
Okay.
Because nobody's going to do that.
I'm like, until they know it's for sure they're fault.
I was going to give you 10 grand.
Yeah.
You know.
So you're going to, like, do you contact their insurance then?
We're going to contact their insurance company, yes.
And then if she admits it's her fault, then it might be faster, right?
It might be faster.
If you need something like fast, because whatever.
Yeah.
Then you want to do.
We want to claim on your insurance, which we would help you with.
Because when we don't want you talking to the insurance company.
Okay.
Um.
Well, you know, the case had a lawyer's fine, right?
Like they gave me like a case had a lawyer something.
You can talk about the property damage.
Okay.
That's I think she's the one I'm scheduling.
Yeah.
My red zone.
But don't talk to them about the injuries or accidents.
You probably did already because they probably call it.
Yeah, they call it right away.
Yeah.
But if they ask you anything else, you know what hired an attorney.
Can you talk to her about it?
Okay.
Got it.
Cool.
Um, but just saying.
I've seen it where they're like.
15 people can say that they saw it, but they're not paying the freaking car until they get that.
Yeah.
Because they don't want to be out of the 10 grand.
Okay.
Um, same thing with the rental car.
You're not going to get one until they say they did it.
So, but if you have it on your car, then we will help you get that rental.
Again, we don't want you talking to me in terms of companies.
Yeah.
And my like, is it possible to get a rental before Tuesday or now?
Possibly if you have that rental car coverage on your car.
Okay.
Yeah.
I could just use mine shirts.
Yes.
Basically that will help you with that.
Yeah.
We'll help you with that.
But we're getting like a reimbursement.
Right.
Exactly.
And if you can't, if we can't do it fast enough, then what you would do is get a rental and then give us the receipt.
Okay.
Yeah.
But you'd have to find a rental where you could drop it off and.
So like, yeah.
It'd be a pain in the ass to have to drive it back.
Yeah.
I'm sure they tried your extra fee for that too.
Maybe I check.
Maybe what you could do is rent it and sell it like.
Yeah.
But then I play and take it kind of like.
No, but if you rent it in Salt Lake, can you return a Salt Lake?
Makes sense.
Yeah.
You probably could.
Because I was just going to drop my dad's car.
But I didn't want to.
I was thinking like maybe get it here and then just give it back to the one I get there.
Or just.
You can rent it in Salt Lake.
You know what I mean?
That's true.
Yeah.
Okay.
Anyway.
So our job is to get you the, you know, most money in the first amount of time.
Which is to make your case look better.
You know, so we have to show that we're injury attorneys who look to show the injuries.
The defendants, you know, like, hey, my client was just minding his own business and then he gets hit and then he gets injured.
Yeah.
Their job is to make you look bad.
Look, your car's fairly damaged not in this case, but.
Yeah.
You aren't hurt.
You aren't treating.
That's how we can show you're not hurt.
You know, that's what the defendants are going to do.
So that's why it's important for you to treat regularly with the chiropractor and your doctor.
Yeah.
Robert, does anybody want to terrify Tommy?
Oops.
Yes.
And there's an information between Davis and his testimony and how the synthetic protein iscrafted so that's what we're going to do.
Exactly.
Total speculation.
Well if the Unterschied between the members now doesn't mean they want to apply, either.
So what happens if you hav to say that then you already have enough of your testimonies in freeze.
So you are going to tell them if you get them on遊戲 it's going to make them more difficult for you because you feel like they tell you to do better than they're being hurt.
You are probably the only place that we can destroy to defeat the victim.
You know what I mean?
Of course now if you trust them.
Yeah.
And lastly, if you trust them, then they'll let you help yourself cause you might't plan a workflow or you can wait
Okay, not so I should just go to like urgent care.
Yeah, there's like one down the street and I news my insurance do have to let them know about
Like that to give them your contact or you know, just give them the insurance and then when you get into with a doctor
Then you would say hey, it was a motor vehicle accident
Whatever. Yeah, I'm just gonna give those receipts to you. Yes. Okay. Okay. So you're gonna get receipts in the mail when you get that and then give it to us
They'll tell them about us at all
Okay, but um, but you should say that you got an accident. So they put it in the records. Okay. Okay, uh
Yeah, don't miss any appointments. So I know you're going to school
So if you need to schedule something like after I don't know if school's nine to five or what? Yeah, it's not a five. Yeah
I find you a doctor. It's
It's all like yeah. Okay, so like they close pretty early nine to five. I know that's why I don't go anywhere else
I guess has everything open late. It's true
One day through Friday
So
Yeah, if you have any significant gaps then they're gonna say that you're not injured because that's their job to make you look bad
Like you can't be injured because you took off a week and they took off two weeks and got it
regularly
Okay, put your doctor about any pain that you're having even if you have to write it down your very first time or second time
Because if you don't mention it till the third time, they'll say it doesn't count. Okay, so I mentioned it right
Yeah, just like when I see my IT guy, I'm like hey, this computer. It's acting funny pop-ups happen
I have viruses and my PDF doesn't work and it doesn't print
Because I have to remember when he comes in I'm like I just want to get him in like at the one time
So I get paid that charge up forever. Yeah, if that becomes that that's charging
Right, so you got to tell your doctor the same thing, you know everything that hurts from so think about
If if they send me a bill, do I pay for it for you? No, you don't have to. Okay, just leave everything as it isn't given to you
Right, okay, so when
Okay, so we're gonna find a doctor that treats on a lean. It's called a lean
Because I don't know kind of insurance. Do you have health insurance?
The health point of Nevada. Yeah, it doesn't work in Utah
So we're gonna get you some doctors that treat on a lean, which is an IOU
Okay, hey, we all get paid at the end of the day. Yeah
So but this one I don't work with the hospital
So you'll have to go to the quick care and get that one and get the receipt and pay your co-pay
So make sure you tell the doctor about everything that hurts the first day or whatever
Pain scores and gaps in treatment
So you don't want your pain scores to vary from like I feel like a seven. I feel like a one
Sometimes they won't pay for anything after one. Yeah, okay, and then we talked about the gaps in treatment with your bad
So your settlement is based on your medical bills
So it's based on three things. What's in your medical bills? What's in your medical records and reasonableness? So
For example
This is what a medical bill looks like
It's got codes on it. You see that so this may be a code for like ice pack or whatever or an injection or an MRI or something
And then they'll say the how how much it is right
So that doesn't give you much information, right? Yeah, so what a record has is like hey
I treated him with a nice pack
He was complaining about his headaches and his neck hurting this back hurting and then I didn't MRI and it's got pumps all over or whatever
So I need that right um, it's not that you need that what I'm saying is that
Because some people don't understand right that it's based on what is on here
So it's based on like the mounts and everything and it's based on what you said to the doctor
Okay, okay, so if you don't say anything to the doctor if you come in every day and say my finger hurts
Yeah, finger hurts finger hurts
They're not going to pay you very much for your finger your tip of your finger hurting because you got to splinter from the dashboard or whatever
Right, they're not going to it's going to based on what you say to the doctor
And the pain scores and whatever that kind of thing
Um
Yeah, so and reasonableness so it's not very reasonable
If you went to the doctor every day complaining about that finger and you've got a million dollars in bills
I'm not paying for your finger being in pain. It's not reasonable any reasonable person would have stopped
You know
So but they'll pay for things that are reasonable like the headaches and your neck pains and your back pains and whatever pains
Okay
Um
Yeah, if you do get the bills from the urgent care that would bring them to me. Okay, or email them to me
Uh
Just those take forever to get
And you want to get into paying that because I don't want you to get that credit because you have a $15 copay or something
Yeah, so this pay oh yeah pay that one but use your insurance so they give you a bill for like 15 bucks or something. Yeah, okay
Um, again, it takes like
15 days to get the police report at quick quickly quick guest to the 15 days and they're not going to say that they didn't tell
They get that police report
Okay, so we're going to be doing things behind the scenes. So we're going to be getting like the police report
We're going to be trying to help you with your property damage
We're going to be researching the policy limits because they don't have to tell us so that lady that hit you
Latest she has key insurance
Ah, that's not good
Okay, so I really need to see what your insurance is really bad. So key insurance is like the cheapest insurance
They have like tears
They have tears of insurance so like, you know, all states like middle tier of like my insurance is like top tier
Kind of like colleges. You want to go to Harvard? Yeah, you know what I mean?
So hers is really crap insurance
Hers is really crap insurance. So you want to see what your insurance is because mine I pay for things like this
So do you ever play backpack?
Yeah, I just do a lot of it. Okay, so you know how I say do you want insurance? Yeah, okay, right?
Never buy it, huh? You never buy it right? No, I'm just saying sometimes you do in this case, you know
I bought insurance for people that don't have enough insurance
So I'm sure people and under-insured people so people that
Driving without insurance driving without not enough insurance because what if I'm in the hospital for
A day at like 10,000. Yeah, you know, so she has crap insurance. So I hope your dad bought good insurance if not you should tell him
I just know the code is like 500
No, it's not that it's like mine is like 502
Mine is like
Like that we're watching your treatment
So we're like calling the doctors. Hey, did you follow the boat or is he treating?
You know, we're proving treatment if they tell us like hey can he get this we're proving it
um
And things like that
So because people call us and they're like are you done yet? I'm like are you done yet? Yeah, because I can't give you half of the stuff
Yeah, you know, I mean, I can't give insurance company key like here's one page
I'll give you another page next month. Yeah, they won't kind of like when it's 80 to 100 percent done is when we submit it
So like basically all the treatments and then the car estimate and everything right
I think you just think they're on ones right some like yeah, so this is what a demand letter looks like, you know
Here's someone's all their medical bills and records. So then I would put you know, remember how we've had the medical bills
Yeah, no big metal records, and then they're like fat like that. They're like that fat
huge, you know, and then we submit it because for two reasons
Um, nobody wants to see half of everything because I would forget what I see last if you told me like here
Here's that I'm like okay. Let me reference it again. I forgot what I saw yesterday. Yeah, you know
They just don't want to do that and the other reason is because we don't want a negative anchor a negative anchor is a low offer
So let's say they only see part of it. They only see five grand of it. So they're like oh, I'll just offer a five grand
And then you give him some more stuff and then he's like well, I can't eat my words. Yeah, now I look like crap if I say that
So it's better not because then he'll be like well, I'll go up a little bit like six grand because they've already started at something
And they don't want to seem like they're lying or going back on their words. So that's what the negative anchor is
So we'd rather show them like everything and like dude here it is give us everything. Yeah, you know
So the people like well, did you get anything done yet? Dude, I have been doing things. It's just
Yeah, I can't show them half of your crap and it's not in your best interest
Um, if you want to come see us, which you probably won't because you're not going to be here
You can call us tech sister email us because we have people that just drop in and like
I'm made yeah
Uh, the number here the number that you just text all those pictures to
I think I can call it you can call the number that's the main number. Yes, there's a main number
Okay, so there's a main number on here and you can definitely call that number
I will give it to you again
Okay
There's a letter
You want to read it? It's got to come one more time before at least just to make sure I got everything
This is it. Oh, I know
I will give it to you
As soon as I figure out where I put it
Do you know like you say it's around like two weeks fastest
I could take up to a month or even
With key yeah
He is crap insurance. So they will they don't care they if you google their ratings
They don't give a shit if you want to complain to the freaking they should be just if there was disfarring of insurance companies
They should be disbarged
Like I've written a nasty letter like my freaking client gave you his title like five months ago and they'll be like
All right
I've got like hundred people yelling at me every day, you know, they're like I don't give a crap
So yeah, he's I would open it under yours
Well, the reimbursement will be one year, but
Because when I first off to my I'll say they tell me like the car either is gonna get fixed or replace with my insurance first
Right, and then they go after them. Yeah, yes, exactly
Separation yes, what's
What if they can't get them like like what's the percentage of them not being able to get them in it?
That's the case I think
Okay, okay, just make sure yeah, yeah, just because if it was like a clear if it was like hey
He said she said it's a red light. It's green light. Yeah, you know that kind of thing
But since there's like five witnesses or whatever
So I don't I just think it's this time to deal with key because key sucks, but other than I think they're rich money. Okay cool
Okay, so
So I'll just send you all the bills. I'll send you the insurance policy
The page I could go picture of okay, cool
Yep, I'm gonna give you a moment, right the estimate and declaration
boop
Any medical bills that come in the mail or that little urgent care bill. Yeah, and don't pay for you. I just have my insurance
Have your insurance that then pay the copay
But also but let them know that it's for an injured like for an accident, right? Let the doctor know so it's in the records, right
patient care copay
Pay it
Just get insurance to pay the top part and then get the copay you pay the copay. Okay
Um, we work as a team
So we may work on your file because people will be like hey, I never you know get to talk to Sandy or whatever or whatever
The usually talk to the
Persons handling the case or their assistant
And then I jump in when there's something so the manager that was on the paper right
And your parents have you changed manager or so, okay, cool
Other than that
Do you have gap insurance or do you owe it? What was that? Oh, it's right there. I'm gonna give it to him. Okay, so do you have a gap insurance or is it car?
It's almost paid off. Not yet. Yeah, they're still so I guess gap. Yeah
Yeah, I'm doing like payments on it like every month
Okay, just need your signature here that you're not a medicare or something because you're not like 60
Is it an effect anything that is not paid off the car or okay, no, it's just people that don't have the
So you want one of those figure out who your lean holder is because they'll probably need to know that when they do lean holder
So whoever's like toyota finance or whatever, you know
Okay, other than that, let's see
Okay, and then I'll if I listen to being just like giving a corner text and I'll try to get it
I'll try to give you like most of everything
Okay, no, I think you got everything. It's just a gift page in the estimate if you get one
Um, and your health insurance
I thought the page was Daniel's insurance
The debt glitch. No. Oh, that's car insurance. I'm like your blue cross your health plan of Nevada. Yeah
I'll do. Wait, what was that the health plan of Nevada? Yeah, health and life. I didn't get a copy of that. Oh, okay
Do you have it with you? No, okay. Yeah, okay. Okay, cool. That's basically it. Okay
And then that
But you just need the card, right? I have like the card. Okay
Yeah
No
Oh wait
You have the same one I like this insurance
My girlfriend's like really? This is better and I'm like, but my doctor's on this insurance
You're getting one. I'm ahead
You
We'll need you to sign this twice for me
We just sign here twice. Sign here. Open the sign here. What was it? I'll fill it up
Pray here. So yeah, you know, print the sign or whatever
Because I would never be able to take that out. Yeah
Okay, do it again. Right there. Yeah, because it was two notaries
Okay
All right
Oh, she got it
Like a DK
So yeah, remember how we talked about blackjack
Okay, so I buy insurance in case someone doesn't have enough insurance. So if I'm in the hospital
You know, let's say I make $100,000 a month or whatever. Yeah, you know, and I'm in the hospital
And I'm like I lost my wages because I was in the hospital and I've got this $100,000 bill
$200,000 worth of
$100,000 for the wage loss and $100,000 for the bill
I have $250,000 worth of insurance. Yeah
So it would go after my own insurance because I bought that for that reason
So we're just hoping that he has the coverage. I'm hoping you have that coverage. Okay, but with that
Nope, it's not there's a state law that says it can't go up. So it goes up and you can play into them
So yeah, you should get this coverage
Anybody else at your house have coverage or is do you have any other insurance or is it just your parent?
Smokers. Yeah, my whole family is the same insurance. Yeah, brother, parents. Yeah. Yeah, this is like very important insurance
Like you need to get this type of insurance
So you also need this information right
Yeah, yeah
There you go
Welcome, let me go get that thing to sign
So
So they're insurance cover and then all insurance
Here you go
Okay, read through it and we can go over with you too
Yeah, sure. This is that I represent you for an accident that occurred five days ago
Wait, five days ago, I mean on the fifth, right? Oh, yeah, sorry
So I met her and then last thing was KWA and
Uh, if we recover something we get a third of it if we have to go to court to recover it
We get 40% of it if we don't recover anything. There is no fee. Okay. I'm gonna be paying for
The cost ahead of time because we're doing things ahead that you don't know about
So like the police report. We're gonna be doing getting that we're gonna also be trying to get the policy limits of her
You know, which I think are probably going to be 15 pretty sure of it um
What else you know if we have to file fees or anything like that postage copies
You can pick any attorney that you want so you can always
Decide to fire us or whatever you want to do
You just have to send us written notice and then we'd get paid for whenever time we've spent on it
So we spend three hours on it time five hundred bucks an hour or whatever we send the bills to your new attorneys
ABC attorneys
Sometimes we might bring on another attorney. So let's say we have to litigate this
Or you've brain damage or something and we need a brain damage attorney. Yeah. Okay. This is probably not gonna have in this case
But you never know um, there is no guarantee as to the results
Services not covered so I can do one trial
So let's see if we go to trial and we go to court and we go do our motions and discovery and everything
And then they decided to appeal to the Supreme Court
Yeah, I have to charge you for that one
Okay, that's like
2% of the cases go to trial and then
Very smaller percentage go to like the Supreme Court or appeals. Okay
Um, I can't give you a loan
Because the state bar doesn't like that
Prove when this is your settlement. I will never settle the case without your authority
So we will talk about it and then we'll say hey, should we counter should we file suit? Whatever
What we do
So I'll never ever settle the case without you
um distribution of funds
We
Once we know what the final number is in the breakdown
Then I'll be like this goes to you this goes to me just goes to the doctors and this and that
So we'll have a little breakdown like a spreadsheet
Okay, and then I do have to pay the doctors don't file bankruptcy not a good idea. Don't think you will
And that's basically it
So the doctors
They get paid because they have to lean remember the island until the end of the accident. Yeah
Sign there
You know what you should read
You should read um
The portable